<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Nikitas Tampakis</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Nikitas Tampakis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflections</title>
      <link>/stories/reflections/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/reflections/</guid>
      <description>While I feel like I have so much more to learn and discover about myself and the surrounding world, I have also reached a certain level of maturity and relative self-awareness.
Despite peaking as a track athlete in 8th grade, in almost all other areas, I notice that I get stronger every year. I have observed this most acutely in my abilities as a singer, but I think part of the reason is that since I have so many recordings of past performances, it is easier for me to directly track and observe my evolution as a performer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US States Wishlist</title>
      <link>/stories/us-states-wishlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/us-states-wishlist/</guid>
      <description>Update January 2024: States I visited since originally posting are crossed out. 18 to go!
Since I started working as a software developer, I have been fortunate to travel extensively throughout the United States for conferences and professional development, but also to see friends who are spread across the country. As many do, one day I hope to visit all 50. With 24 states left, I have ranked the remaining states below ordered by how much excitement I have to explore each place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-meta* Personal Archiving</title>
      <link>/stories/post-meta-personal-archiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/post-meta-personal-archiving/</guid>
      <description>What better way to my first post than with a meta-post? My experience working for a library has been all about a becoming metadata master. Learning the language used by research institutions to describe its vast collections is like possessing the keys to all knowledge. While the human brain has limited storage capabilities, every so often it captures something extraordinary, worth preserving in written word to share with others. With the stories section of this website, I offer glimpses into my daily experiences with the hope that they will be entertaining and maybe even useful.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>